Okay, so now we're going to look at finishing off
the the side of the base, so if I only put the
Core shadow in
Now we need to look for the
transition
So take a red for red
Green it's looking around this your line. Let's soften that edge
Violent shape
Because it comes from the chin it's a bit lighter
This accent in here coming back into that
darker transitional
So I'm just going to pick out that back in that edge
The front plane so that's cheek
chin
Shape it's quite kind of yellowy. I'm just mixing that
No role
It's got darker green or yellow
If we're finding chin going to come back in a bit lighter
So that's front plane of the chin. Just looking at
She ran there and back in with that this light shape I was using to show the front plane
The chin okay more green
darker
I'm looking at this top plane
That connects the yellowish side some illiterate green
Bit darker than that we use this from for the front plane cheek
Chin sorry we're going a bit lighter and the current looking at the
Tattoo cheek case and it's going to go with this shape again. It's almost a full
illiterate green
Just check that a bit too dark a bit of light
Yellow into that
Too light now on the red side or right into that with that shape
then
It's gonna look for this
Shape around here and be a bit lighter a bit more yellow in there
It makes sense enough with that edge
It kind of comes up there and bring in this core shadow, but this next
I'm just going to reinstate that
She there again
Mid-to-dark alizarin it's a green lighter
It'll be that comes up around the cheek. I guess like a lighter looking to soften these
Pick out these light slides a shape
But more on the green side a little bit more
A little bit more in that edge from the big amount of catch
Okay
And kind of brother temple by a lighter on the red side
Look at the front plane
to
shape around the mouth around the
Front plane so looking at this shape here now, but we're looking at that a shape there to be
yellow
laser in a
Touch of green
Bring that light to shape in there look at this slight darker
tone
Hey, I'm gonna soften this edge. Yeah, it's like a light yellow back around with this
So let's now look at this from playing the cheek. Look at this shape in here
So look at these lighter shapes
Front of the face this yellow
Doesn't green the long side right in there. So I'm going to say that's the
Front side plane